How to remove items in the queue deck.
It's not the queue, so this method is called deck.
It's start by removing the deck, so if I have this queue.
Three to one, the first element that I have inserted is one.
So there were removed the first element that it is insert if I call the method deck.
Again, it was removed there, too.
And again, deck were removed.
Three.
Let's see encoding how this works.
Removing items in queue or deck.
Start by.
Define the size three and array size and in-front equals zero and entry are equal to zero.
We use the method deck.
We have to check if front, equal, equal to rear.
Then queue is empty.
Otherwise, it will print the deck element.
Array at front, and we increase front by one.
How this works.
After reaching the after making this stack as full or if you have elements in the stack, we start by
check it, which we call the deck.
We remove that element.
So how this algorithm work, we start checking a front equal, equal to rear.
No front is at index zero and rear is an index three.
Then, if it's not executed, the Elsbeth would be executed.
Print f would be that element at the console.
You will get that element 100 in the console and the front will be increased by one.
Again, if I called the deck, it would check from equal, equal to rear.
No front is equal to one and rear is equal to three.
It will execute the LS part.
It will print on the screen deck element equal to 200.
And it will increase the front by one.
Again, if I call Method Deck, it will call check.
Front equal, equal to rear.
No front equal to two.
And rear equal to three.
Then the l'esposizione position and else part will be executed.
It will print on the screen text element equal to 300, and it will remove it from that way, and the
front will be increased by one.
If I call the method deck now, it will it will check if front equal to rear.
Yes.
So front is equal to three and four year is equal to three.
Then stop and the print queue is empty.
OK.
This is the algorithm of removing items in the queue is known as back, by the way, removing and adding
items in the queue.
And the best case is of of one.
And in the worst case is of one.
This is the very, very big advantage of using the stacks and the queues in terms of time complexity,
because adding and removing items will cost you both one.